gentlemint.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy

### Your privacy is critically important to us. At Brisky Business we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We may ask you for trivial personal information like ' _What's your favorite MacGyver episode_?' because, well we **truly need it**. But the aforementioned "important stuff" we'll leave alone.) 
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights. Because that's what any true gentleman would do.
  * We don’t store personal information (moustache length, etc.) on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Brisky Business, LLC. ("Brisky Business") operates gentlemint.com. It is Brisky Business' policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Brisky Business collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Brisky Business' purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Brisky Business' visitors use its website. From time to time, Brisky Business may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Brisky Business also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on Gentlemint.com. Brisky Business only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that page commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the page where the comment was left.

#### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Brisky Business' websites choose to interact with Brisky Business in ways that require Brisky Business to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Brisky Business gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at Gentlemint.com to provide a username and email address. In each case, Brisky Business collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Brisky Business. Brisky Business does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

#### Aggregated Statistics

Brisky Business may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Brisky Business may monitor the most popular users or pages on the Gentlemint.com site. Brisky Business may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Brisky Business does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Brisky Business discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Brisky Business’ behalf or to provide services available at Brisky Business' websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Brisky Business' websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Brisky Business will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Brisky Business discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Brisky Business believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Brisky Business, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Brisky Business website and have supplied your email address, Brisky Business may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Brisky Business and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Brisky Business takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Brisky Business uses cookies to help Brisky Business identify and track visitors, their usage of Brisky Business website, and their website access preferences. Brisky Business visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Brisky Business' websites, with the drawback that certain features of Brisky Business' websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

#### Business Transfers

If Brisky Business, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Brisky Business goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Brisky Business may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

#### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Brisky Business and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated infromation (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Brisky Business may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Brisky Business' sole discretion. Brisky Business encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a Gentlemint.com account, you should also check your account for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
